<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="7"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[How to use



                                     support system]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[How to use support system


                   1.  Go to link: ambsupport.com then login.



























                                           Dashboard and Task Tracking
                   2.  After login you will see “Dashboard”, this is all your case summary.]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[3.  How to add issue, please go to menu 1.2 Task Tracking.
                       -  Click on +Add button to add new task. Please provide all detail for the support
                          team to have a perfect quality check on yours issue.
                       -  Please don’t forget to save.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[4.  After add task, your task will appear here.
                       -  You also can monitor that’s your task got pick-up by our support team yet or not.
                       -  After our support team pick-up task, you will see the who’s pick-up and average /
                          estimate end date.






















                   5.  You can also see comment from our support team here, by clicking on button.
                       -  If have any comment, it will notify you by red dot.








                       -  You also can reply back to our support team, after chat please click on “Save”.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[6.  After case solved, our support team will close case and you will got notify here.
                       -  You have to “Acknowledge” case close by clicking on Acknowledge button.













                       -  After acknowledged, this task will disappear.


                                                     Management
                   1.  How to add sub-agent.
                       -  Clicking on menu 2.1 Add Sub Agent.
                       -  Enter all require field, then click on “Add Sub Agent” button.


























                       -  Edit sub-Agent here.













                       -  Add member and Edit Member also same with Sub-Agent.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Announcement

                   1.  You can see announcement from our side here.
                       -  The default date is today, you also can search by date filter.
                       -  Click on image button to see attached files.































                                                      Feedback
                   1.  Please provide your feedback to us here.
















                       -  This is your previous feedback.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[]]></page></pages></Search>